# Roniya Rojan

Detroit, MI | roniyarojan24@gmail.com | 248-202-9680 | github.com/ronithrojan | linkedin.com/in/roniya-rojan

# Summary

Attraction to web development started at a young age for me. Out of curiosity, I sat down with my peers to observe them as they worked on their personal developmental projects. Over the years, that curiosity transitioned into learning basic programming from experienced family members. The little victories that came from practicing coding ultimately resulted in my decision to end my pre-medical journey and pursue software engineering as a full-time career.

# **Education**

#### **Grand-Circus Front End Bootcamp**

 ${\tt Matching\ Game\ -\ JavaScript,\ TypeScript,\ HTML5/CSS}$ 

Front-End Website - HTML5/CSS, JavaScript

Event-Master - AngularJS, TypeScript, HTML5/CSS

 $NBA\ Trivia\ App-AngularJS,\ TypeScript,\ Node.js/Express,\ SQL,\ Web\ APIs,\ JavaScript,$ 

HTML5/CSS

Wayne State University, Bachelor of Science in Public Health

05/2019 Detroit, Michigan

01/2020 - 03/2020

Detroit, Michigan

#### **Skills**

• HTML/CSS

Javascript

• Angular

· Node.js

• Git/GitHub

Typescript

SQL
 Web APIs

Data Analysis

# **Professional Experience**

## **Detroit Receiving Hospital,** *Undergraduate Research Assistant*

05/2017 - 12/2019

- Oversaw 35 cardiovascular studies in addition to stroke studies to pinpoint root causes through analysis of blood samples
- Developed and organized 500 + records and maintenance reports to increase the efficiency of the work environment, resulting the reduction of study periods by 3-4 months
- Presented performance reports and found levels of troponin I proteins high in patients who
  have lack of diet and physical activity coupled with second hand smoke exposure

#### **CorkTown Health Clinic,** Public Relations Intern

08/2016 - 05/2017

- Created marketing materials to familiarize the public on (PrEP) to prevent HIV risk and Pride Month, which increased attendance by 75%
- Planned and coordinated panels on public health concerns for LGBT for audience of 20-30 undergraduates bi-weekly
- Increased patient enrollment by 60% through active communication through social media accounts.

#### **High Program,** Data Entry Operator

09/2015 - 02/2016

- Received over \$50,000 for donations through consistent communications with public organizations and private donors
- Compiled and documented statistical information for donations through in-person meetings increasing more donors.
- Responsible for handing a high volume of inbound customer request per day